<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PitchTrainer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">Pitch Trainer</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Pitch Trainer</string>
    <string name="tutorial_label">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "This app is made to train and test Relative Pitch.\n"
        "Relative Pitch is a person's ability to identify intervals between two or more notes.\n"
        "Start by selecting a difficulty with the slider, there is a text below that describes this"
        "difficulty.\n The recommendation is to start with difficulty 1 and work your way 1 by 1."
        "\nMost people will find the first couple of difficulties sufficiently challenging.\n\n"
        "Press 'Start PitchTrainer' and 'Play Phrase' to start.\n You will hear 2 or more notes, "
        "depending on the difficulty chosen.\n The first note is shown in blue, the rest of the"
        "notes are unknown.\n It is your job to try to guess the unknown notes in the Phrase.\n"
        "Pressing a note on the keyboard will register a guess.\n"
        "If the guess is correct the pressed key will turn green,"
        "if the guess is incorrect the pressed key will turn red\n. If the phrase consists of multiple"
        "unknown notes, you will have to keep guessing at the next note in the phrase until you have"
        "guessed all notes correctly, or until you have gotten one incorrect guess.\n"
        "At any time you can press 'Replay Phrase' to listen to the Phrase again.\n This is recommended"
        "if you are not sure of which note to guess on.\n After you have guessed the Phrase (correctly,"
        "or incorrectly) you can press any key to hear it's note.\n This can help you build intuition"
        "of the keyboard.\n You can always press 'New Phrase' to generate and guess on a new random phrase.\n"
        "If you want to change difficulty or view this tutorial you can press the left arrow"
    </string>
</resources>